One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
The Mastermind in the Shadows and the
Battle Between Gas and Rubber!
Little White Hunter, for the time being you'll have to keep your hands off Caesar.
If they start crushing our hearts we'll be at an enormous disadvantage,
so I can't allow you to do as you please until I have my heart back from Vergo.
While you're on this island you'll have to follow my orders, understand?
This was the shortest path and I got here as fast as possible.
Where are you, Vergo!?
You stubborn bastard!
Gotcha!
No, you haven't!
Combustion Type!
Miok Gas!
Straw Hat!
What do you hope to gain by attacking me!?
I don't know yet! But if I capture you now then something interesting is gonna start!
So you formed an alliance!? Did Law suggest that? You can't trust that guy at all, you know!
He's gonna betray you for sure! Don't do it!
Something like that is for me to decide!
You want more pain, you rubber bastard!?
Airless World!
I can't breathe!
That's right!
I'm safe back here!
That's right, there's a fixed range where you can't breathe!
But, can you stay at that distance forever?
Rubber...
Jet Pistol!
That hurt, dammit!
However, if you come any closer you're gonna choke!
Not again!
Does it hurt? Watch this, here's all the oxygen!
Blue Sword!
Again!
Watch this! You're gonna burn to ash!
I can manipulate all gases! If poison gas won't work there are plenty of other ways to attack you!
Armanent Hardening!
Wha—
Rubber...
Jet Gatling!
What's this!? A wall?
Snow Hut.
Quite impressive, an average pirate couldn't break this wall.
Huh? Are you an ability user?
Master, you should go, this is a pointless fight.
It certainly is.
Are you running away!?
So long, Straw Hat, you can fight as much as you like now!
I've already thought of the perfect way to include you all in the experiment!
I hope you're looking forward to it!
Wait!
I won't let you chase him.
If master were to have an accident,
Joker would kill me.
The bird-guy I saw during the war? What does he have to do with all this!?
Connecting Passage for Buildings A & B
Hurry up! The gate is closing!
Run!
Is that the Straw Hat crew's Black Leg!?
Why the hell is he helping us!?
Stomach...
Strike!
Whoa, he's strong!
Black Leg from the Straw Hat crew is fighting that fake Vergo!
We've gotta back him up!
What're you guys doing!? Get outta here!
Once this place is locked down they're gonna flood it with poison gas!
See, I told you!
That deadly gas is coming in! Run!
Right, it looks like this guy's body is made of iron or something like that.
Stay out of my way. This is between me and them.
You're the type of scum our captain hates the most.
This guy...!
Hey, Black Leg bro!
The gate is closing! Quickly, get over here!
The poison gas is already right behind you! Hurry up!
This is Building D! This is Building D!
This is an emergency message to all buildings in the third laboratory!
What's this!?
This is Building D! This is an emergency message to all buildings in the third laboratory!
One of the Seven Warlords, Trafalgar Law, has just entered the SAD production room!
What the hell!? Is that bastard totally insane!?
If he actually interferes with this then he's going to be sorry!
That's what he was up to!
What the hell!?
Kidnapping the Master? Then the SAD will...
I can see what you're trying to do now.
Law joined up with Straw Hat in order to launch a counterattack!
He became one of the Seven Warlords just to get inside that room!
SAD Production Room
That little bastard!
He must be plotting the worst possible scenario!
Does he really intend...
to completely unbalance the New World!?
Connecting Passage for Buildings A & B
I repeat! The traitor, Trafalgar Law has...
Wait! Don't close the gate!
That fake Vergo and Black Leg bro are still in there!
It closed!
There's nothing we can do! The other side of the gate will be totally filled with that lethal gas!
Black Leg!
Bro!
Black Leg bro!
Hey! Are you alright!? You are the Navy's...
That's...!
cutest girl ever!
Black Leg!
Hell yeah, Black Leg bro!
I'm so glad you're alive!
We're so grateful!
Shut up, you pack of bastards! Look, I'll only listen to the lilting cheer of girls!
Hey, Black Leg, we're really glad that you're not hurt!
Shut up! I only accept care and sympathy from girls!
That was dangerous. If that fight had kept going...
Anyway, what's up with that guy? Isn't he your superior officer!?
No way!
That bastard isn't Vice Admiral Vergo!
He's an impostor!
Ain't that right, Captain-chan?
Yes, of course! The real Vergo wouldn't do that to you guys, he's like a loyal parent to you all!
He'd never do anything like that.
Impostor or not, his expression changed and then he suddenly disappeared.
We've gotta hurry, too!
We have to save the children and get them out of here!
Yeah!
We're right behind you, Captain-chan!
Building B Interior
Law's after the SAD!?
Yes. It's clear now that Law has betrayed us.
The New World, Dressrosa
That's what I figured!
I thought of him as my brother.
One of the Seven Royal Warlords of the Sea
Donquixote Doflamingo (Black Market Broker: Joker)
I watched over him carefully as he grew up.
Too bad.
I understand.
He's in the SAD production room?
If I were in his shoes, the first thing I'd do is wreck the whole room.
And then kidnap Caesar?
Nah, I'd probably just kill him.
After all, Caesar is the only person in the world
who knows how to properly prepare the SAD.
Still, if he does do this, I'll be in a lot of trouble, Vergo.
If Caesar is killed then there's no one else who can make the gas. That'll be bad for my business.
Try relaxiin', Baby 5, what're you doiin' to our poor master?
I'm not gonna forgive him this time! I'm gonna kill this filthy bastard!
And if I get into trouble? What happens after that?
Oiin!
After that comes...
a series of unfortunate events!
What do you intend to do about our cute youngster Law-chan, young master?
It's quite clear that he's rebelling against us, don't you agree, young master?
It must be painful for you, Vergo, but please get rid of Law right now.
He must be made to regret that he was ever born into this world. Make his death truly unpleasant.
I understand.
I'll even take a photo of the corpse for you to see, Doffy.
I can use the camera that I bought in Dressrosa.
You didn't even buy a camera in Dressrosa, did you?
That's right, I didn't buy a camera at all.
In that case I'll bring you one of his ears.
I can't wait!
Caesar, Monet, are you listening?
Yes, Joker.
Oh, Joker!
Law is a given, but you must be wary of Straw Hat, he has awakened the Conqueror's Haki within him.
His abilities may be even greater than Law's.
I have the perfect hotblooded lady hanging around here.
I'll be sending Baby 5 and Buffalo over there now.
When this mess is over you must all come to Dressrosa.
Of course.
Understood.
Building B Interior - Brownbeard Bus and Passengers
Man, this little dragon is even more trouble than that big one. He's really nimble.
Then what're you lying around for!?
Stop the damn dragon!
Building B is already a sea of flames.
If we let him carry on like that and one of these tanks explodes...
Then the walls might break and that deadly gas will come flooding inside!
If that happens then there's no way that anyone will survive!
Wait, everyone!
I cannot allow myself to back down from this dragon!
I bear a grudge against him!
With my own two hands I swear—
No, no, I'm the one who can't forgive what that dragon has done!
You all saw it, didn't you? His terrible behavior earlier!
He charged right in, wanting to eat me...
Right before my very eyes he gave me such a disappointed look!
You're not exactly food though, are you?
Even bones have nutrition, you know!
Alright, sure, I'll bear that in mind.
Kin'emon-san, please let me deal with this!
What are you saying!? You must step back now!
No, I'll do it!
It will be me!
I will!
With a one, and a two and a nin, nin, nin!
What ever are you doing?
Being a samurai!
That's a ninja!
Here he comes!
Thunder Trap!
My opponent!
Breast band girl, you can use ninja skills!?
Stop calling me that!
Eat this! The foulest smelling flower in the world!
Deadly Green Star! Rafflesia!
Whoa! So, even the puppy-faced goblin can use witchcraft!
Who're you callin' a goblin!?
Forty Flowers! Four Hands!
Hold!
Even the courtesan uses witchcraft!
He's falling! I'll finish him off!
Never! Leave him to me!
Follow after me, Corpse-dono!
Foxfire Style! Conflagration Cutter!
He cut fire again!
Nice work!
Nothing of the sort.
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
Gavotte Forward Leap
Flaming Fox Flourish!
Who're you calling a corpse?
Ah, I guess I am a corpse.
Alright!
We did it.
Perfect victory!
Please say "bones are tasty"!
Damn this irritating dragon!
Bastard, bastard!
I had good reason, but Kin'emon-san, why're you beating him like he's your parent's worst enemy?
He's as good as my parent's worst enemy!
Hey, wait, wait...
Both of you get back on quickly or we'll leave you behind!
Ah, wait for us, please!
Wait a minute! Look at that!
That voice!
Chopper's transformed into a monster!
What the heck is he doing!?
Building B 2nd Floor - Examination Room
Alright, there doesn't seem to be any problem.
You can go back to the Biscuit Room now.
Really?
There's candy there for you.
Yay!
Hey, I was thinkin', where'd that other kid go?
Other kid?
Yeah.
He went to the secret room you shouldn't go to.
Then he turned into a little dragon.
That boy Momonosuke did.
Translation & initial syncing, Kousei Fansubs
Syncing, Galaxy 9000, , Sync-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Title card artist, lucas2265